We have arrived(到达)
at the dawn of a new era.
We will face the unknown
together.
I don't know what it is,
but there's plenty of people
out here
trying(尝试) to figure it out.
You know I've got your backIve(伊夫)u know I've got your back.
Damn well better,
I'm your captain.
We have to work together.
For the good of
the new Belter(了) state.
Detective Miller
crashed(崩溃) into Venus.
I'm just an investigator now.
I find things(事情).
Couple hundred billion
brain cells(细胞) in your skull.
When I push a few trillion(万亿)
of them buttons(按钮)
in exactly the right way,
you're talking(说话) to Miller.
Miller showed(显示) me things(事情).
A whole civilization.
They made(成) the station,
this space.
Something killed them.
They tried(试) to stop it.
Burned(烧焦了) whole solar systems(系).
Only, it didn't work.
When we detonated(引爆) our bomb,
I believe
we became(成为) the threat.
We taught(教) the station
that our ships(的)
are(的) fusion(聚变) bombs(炸弹).
We need to shut down every
reactor in the flotilla(船队).
That station is gonna(要)
wipe us all out,
unless we make this
happen now.
Together till the end?
We're on the brink(边缘) right noWere(的)re on the brink right now
because we keep reacting(反应) to
things we don't understand!
And we're reaching(在)
for violencwere(曾经) we're reaching
for violence
because we can't figure out
what to docant(斜面)ause we can't figure out
what to do.
Don't shoot!
Fuck(操).
You've given us
a new frontier,
1,300 habitable(可居住) systems(系统) on
the other side of those rings(环).
It's gonna(将) be another
blood-soaked gold rush.
The civilization that built(的)
the rings(环) is gone, wiped(的) out.
What could have killed them?
That's what
I'd like to know.
Gonna(要) need a ride.
Unidentified
Belter(不) ships(的),
you are(在) entering(进入)
restricted(限制) space.
Veer(转向) off now, or we will fire!
Barbapiccola,
this is the UNN( ) Tripoli.
Shut down your drive now,
or we will fire.
Respond immediately.
We are(是) unarmed(没有武器).
This is a refugee ship.
Mama(妈妈), I'm scared.
Whatever happens(发生),
we will be together.
Together.
Tripoli,
you are(的) not authorized(授权)
to fire inside the Ring Space.
Barbapiccola, the OPA
orders(命令) you to comply.
We will not.
We've been(一直) begging(乞求)
for a port
since Ganymede(Ganymede) fell.
No one would let us land.
If you're going to kill us,
just do it now, or let us go!
Go.
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Now, that's
a good cup of coffee.
Did(过) you speak to Naomi?
It was lovely meeting her,
except it was through a screen.
It's such a shame she couldn't
come down and see the farm.
Mom(妈妈)...
That was a long trip
you were(的) on.
She could have taken(采取) those
gravity drugs(药物) on the way.
It's not that easy.
Those drugs(毒品) are(是) brutal.
I wouldn't have asked(问) her
to do that for me.
And this isn't her homeisnt(不是) this isn't her home.
Most Belters(数) have mixed
feelings(感情) about Earth.
Here.
It's for your next long haul.
Think I need to reread(重读) this?
What did(曾经) you see out there?
It's hard to put into words(语).
Storm's comingStorms(暴风雨)'s coming.
Mm(嗯).
I'm gonna(要) go
close up the house.
I'll be right in.
Gonna(Gonna) be a real
turd-floater, huh?
Perfect words(的)
for every occasion.
Hey.
We gotta(得走了) talk about that ride.
The ride?
Yeah, I know.
Next clue to the case.
We're leaving(离开) tomorrowWere(曾经是)re leaving tomorrow.
Are(是吗) we going to the Ring?
We're going to New York.
What the hell's(地狱) in New York?
Tall buildings(的),
good pizza,
Secretary-General
of the United Nations(国)SecretaryGeneral(秘书长)al
of the United Nations,
who summoned(召唤) me.
So you can ask her,
tell her to let you
go through the Ring.
I have, a hundred times.
I'll bring it up again,
but something must have changed(变化)
if she wants(想) to talk.
We gotta(得走了) talk
about that ride, kid.
Next clue to the case.
I wonder what that rain
tastes(味) like.
I used to love the rain
when I was a kid.
I'd sit out here and watch
the lightning storms(暴风雨).
Sounds(声音) beautiful.
We gotta(得走了) talk
about that ride, kid.
Next clue to the case.
You got it, Miller.
I'll take care of it.
I hope we get a chance
to meet in person one day.
You know, I'm quite a dancer.
Holden never stops(停) saying(说).
Fong(方) kopenga
tolwanda ert(电化学反应堆) el Belte
fong(方) kopenga tolowabda Ert(化学反应堆).
Okay, okay, okay.
- Bye, now.
- Bye!
- Bye-bye!
- Bye! Take careByebye(再见)-bye!
- Bye! Take care!
That was agonizing(痛苦).
Yes, it was.
I'll see you soon.
Love you.
New railgun's looking(的) good.
I just need you to check out
the thrust compensator(补偿器).
If thing's not tied
into our drive just rightthings(情),
we're all gonna(要) get
tossed(扔) into the ceiling
every time it fires(火).
I'm on it.
Hey, Amos.
Melba?
Please, Clarissa.
I get one vid(Vid) message
a month now.
I...
didn't have anyone to call.
- Okay.
- So you coming down the well?
Nope(没有).
Not even to feel the surf(海浪)
through your toes(脚趾)?
There's a lot of past
in my pastTheres(有)'s a lot of past
in my past.
I'm gonna(要) skip it.
At least you have the choice.
I'm gonna(要) spend the rest
of my life in here.
Like Dad.
Yeah, they really
threw(的) the book at you.
I called(叫) to say thank you.
For what?
The months(月) heading home,
letting(让) me work
in the shop with you,
- it kept(保持) me sane(正常的).
- You're a good mechanic.
I've been(一直) thinking
about somethingIve(伊夫)ve been thinking
about something.
Remember when you sent(去) me
to check on the...
the seals(密) in the air lock?
Yep.
The safeties(安全)
had(有) been(一直) overridden, and...
if I wanted(的) to, I could have
blown(的) the outer door
while I was in it,
killed myself.
Yep.
Was that on purpose?
If I was staring(着) down
a lifetime sentence,
I'd want to have the option.
It was kind of you
to make the offer.
But Anna was right. I...
I don't deserve
the easy way out.
Stop it.
You breathe in,
you breathe out,
eat, shit, sleep,
you take whatever
they give you,
and you give nothing in return.
I have to go.
They have me doing
dream therapy.
I don't really
understand it, but...
the doctor has(有) flowers(医)
in her office,
and I can smell them
through the glass.
Good luck with that.
Can I bother you
again sometime?
Sure thing, Peaches(桃).
What I want is more ships(的)
at the Ring blockade(封锁).
All I need from you
is to make that happen.
Our assets(资产)
in the outer planets(行星)
have been(一直) decimated(灭).
We don't have the ships(船).
We could redeploy(重新部署)
elements(元素) of the Home Fleet.
You forgot(忘记) about Mars?
It's a new day.
We're all friends(友) nowWere(的)s a new day.
We're all friends now.
Madam(女士) Secretary, if I may...
Nancy, don't start
this shit with me again.
Half our population
is unemployed(失业),
and we've been(的) given
the biggest(最大的) opportunity
to give them jobs(工作), to give them
a purpose in a century.
Every week, another colony ship
filled(装满) with our constituents(的)
shows(显示) up at the blockade(封锁),
and we make them wait.
They're sitting(的) ducks(的)
for pirates(海盗).
They want to explore
new worlds(世界).
We should let them.
When Columbus arrived(到达的),
at least he knew(的) what was
waving(的) at him(他) was human.
We've sent(过) out hundreds(数百)
of probes(探测器) through the Rings(环).
Not one of them has(现) turned(转动) up
any little green men.
You haven't seen(看到) it yet,
so it doesn't exist.
That's your argument?
You can't control
a goddamn(该死的) gold rushcant(斜面) can't control
a goddamn gold rush.
When the stacks(堆) of body bags(袋)
came(的) back from the Yukon,
thousands(千) of hopeful(希望的) idiots(白痴)
lined(具) up to be
the next corpses(尸体).
The only reason there weren't
any riots(骚乱) in the streets(街)
when we fired( )
on the Ganymede(Ganymede) ships( )
was because they were(曾经) Belters(人).
Sooner or later, an Earth ship
will try to run the blockade(封锁).
Are(的) you going to shoot down
our own citizens(公民),
or are(的) we gonna(要) turn this
situation to our advantage?
We are(的) going to do
what I goddamn(的) said(的)
we are(的) going to do.
So do it.
Are(是吗) you familiar
with the Barbapiccola?
Refugee ship from Ganymede(Ganymede).
One of the four that slipped(的)
through the Ring
before the blockade(封锁) went(去) up.
They were(曾经) never
heard(听到) from again.
We heard(的) from them again.
The Belters(elter) have been(e)
installing(安装) comm relays(el)
through the Ring gates,
prioritizing(优先)
those four systems(系统).
The relays(继电器) went(去) live
two days(天) ago
and started(开) picking(开) up
broadcasts(广播) from one system.
By some miracle, the Belters(的)
on this world survived(幸存).
About a hundred or so.
They're calling(呼叫)
the planet Ilus.
Makes(制造) sense.
Ilus was a brother
of Ganymede(Ganymede).
Who gives(给) a fuck(他妈)?
I didn't bring you here
to teach me mythology(神话).
The planet is practically
made(成的) of lithium(锂).
They're mining(采矿) it.
Belters(人) struck(击中) it rich.
Good for them.
They also found this.
That looks(看) like the work
of the protomolecule.
Doesn't appear to be active.
And for a few hundred years(年),
we thought Phoebe was just
a ball of ice orbiting(的) Saturn.
I want you to go to Ilus.
Are(在) you still talking(说话)
to Miller?
It's more like he talks(会谈) to me.
You said(的) the worlds(世界)
on the other side
of those Rings(的) were(的) killed...
genocide(种族灭绝) on a scale
that we cannot(无法) even being
to comprehend(理解).
You have the insight
to the protomolecule
that no one else does(人).
I need to know what is really
going on over there.
Is Ilus a ghost town
or another fucking Eros?
And if it is another Eros?
Evacuate(疏散) the Belters(人),
destroy the protomolecule
if you can,
and get the hell out of there.
Nice of Avasarala to clear up
our salvage(打捞) claim.
- How'd she look?
- Fine.
No, I mean, like,
what was she wearing(穿)?
It's good to be home.
Avasarala's worried it could
become another Eros.
If Miller's right, it could
be something much worse(的)Millers(的)ler's right, it could
be something much worse.
She already has(在) a ship
en route, the Edward Israel.
It's a science ship,
survey vessel out of Titan(泰坦).
- A warship's more her style.
That's for surewarships(战舰)ship's more her style.
That's for sure.
It's not
a military operation.
They've got the gear
and the expertise to assess
the situation and hopefully
contain any contamination(污染).
We'll have access to their
resources(资源) if we need them.
Look, I opened(打开) those gates.
So I'm responsible if
anything comes(来) through them.
We all opened(打开) those gates.
All right.
At Ilus, Amos and I will
transfer to the Edward Israel
and take their shuttle
down to the surface.
Naomi, you and Alex will
stay in orbit on the Roci...
I'm going to the surface too.
Are(是吗) you sure?
It's a long trip to Ilus.
I'll have time to prepare.
There's 1,300
new systems(系统) out thereTheres(有)'s 1,300
new systems out there,
and I don't want
to see them all from orbit.
All right, then,
in which case,
we're gonna(要) need to rig(装) the
Roci for an unassisted(无) landingwere(曾经)re gonna need to rig the
Roci for an unassisted landing.
- I know a guy on Luna.
Give him(他) a call.
So this guy
does(做) MCRN retrofits( 翻新)?
Uh-huh, works cheap and
fast, doesn't ask questions(问题)Uhhuh(嗯哼)uh, works cheap and
fast, doesn't ask questions.
Naomi...
Whatever happens(发生) down there,
we'll deal with it together.
Arriving(达)
at Innis(女名女子名) Shallows( ) Station.
Stand clear of the doors(门).
Civilian
Accountability(责) Committee
reminds(提醒) all citizens(市民) that
your quarterly(季度) action report
is due in two weeks.
The assistance desk is open
for 24(24小时) hours(小时) and 2/23(23)he assistance desk is open
for 24(24小时) hours(小时) and 2/3
for your questions(问题)
and concerns(的).
Don't miss
your deadline.
Mars is better for everyone
when everyone does(工作) their part.
Bobbie.
See you, Rana.
Hey, I got a few bites(咬)
on apartments(公寓),
so I shouldn't be
too much longer.
As long as you need, Bobbie.
I'm gonna(要) shower
and head out for a pop.
Keep an eye out for David?
Sure.
Hey, sit down.
Stay awhile(一会儿).
Can't.
Got a study dateCant(斜面)'t.
Got a study date.
Huh. Pretty good.
Thank you.
Yeah, I can really
heat 'em(Em) up.
Shit, she's earlyshes(的)t, she's early.
Hey, Leelee.
Let me get my stuff.
Hey?
You're Aunt Bobbie.
David talks(会谈) about you
all the time.
He says(说) you're a war hero.
He's a sweet kidHes(的)'s a sweet kid.
Uh, you ready?
It's nice to meet you.
Hey, Bobbie.
Nice to see you, flyboy(飞).
I'm just passing
through the neighborhood,
thought I'd check in live
for a change.
How you doing?
- Getting(得) by.
- Oh, yeah?
I saw(去) the news
you're heading to the Ring.
Are(是吗) you going to New Terra(地)?
I can neither confirm
nor deny that.
There's protomolecule
down thereTheres(有)'s protomolecule
down there.
Yeah, so it would appear.
Appare(的)ntly we are experts(专家)
in the field,
so who better to go
and see for sure, right?
And how are(是) you
feeling about it?
You wouldn't understand.
What's that supposed to mean?
You've never been(过) scared
of anything in your life.
Sure, I have.
All the time.
But there's a tricktheres(有)here's a trick.
You just have to believe
that what you're doing
really matters(的),
and then the fear
can't control youcant(斜面) then the fear
can't control you.
Oh, shit.
Delay's getting(得到) badDelays(延迟)hit.
Delay's getting bad.
Shit.
Take care of yourself, flyboy(飞).
You too, Bobbie.
UN freighter( )
Amberjack( ),
we got you target lock.
Give us cargo.
We no fight and you live.
Answer now.
Unidentified pirata,
this is O.P.A.S. TynanOPAS( )dentified pirata,
this is O.P.A.S. Tynan.
We have target lock.
Shut down your drive.
Prepare to be boarded(登上).
Comply, or we will be forced(被迫)
to fire.
You rabbiting(兔子), bossmang.
Fo da shasa.
Ready the grapple(抓).
Radiation spiking(尖峰).
Evasive(规避) action!
They're dumping(倾倒) core!
Supicon.
Someone go out.
What faction are(的) you with?
It pay well?
Fo kill your own...
fo da Inners(内)?
Three UN supply ships(船)
got hit on this trade route
in one month.
Who is ignoring(忽视) the truce(休战)?
The one that still fight
for the Belt.
Guess you the Inners(的)'
good little koyo now.
Content for the table scraps(残羹剩饭).
They keep Belters(人)
out of the Ring
so they find the gold first,
leave us with dirt.
And you help them.
Good little koyo.
Rocinante,
you are(在) entering(进入)
the Ring Blockade(封锁) Zone.
Please transmit
your access code.
Roger that.
There you go, partner.
Code received(接收)
and verified(证).
You're clear for transit.
It's nice to know Martians(火星人)
have to go through
this as well.
Yeah, but they get to train
for years( ) in one G.
How am I doing?
Good.
Bone density, muscle mass,
heart-lung capacity all up.
They send
a mining(采矿) company
- under the name of science...
- You need a break?
...to steal our land,
the legitimate claim
of our people.
They call Belters(的) terrorists(恐怖分子)
to strip us of our rights(权利).
We all lost family on Ganymede(Ganymede)
because of the Inners(内)' war.
- Yeah.
- Ilus is our home now,
and we will not
be driven(去) out again.
Yeah.
Keep going.
Hmm(嗯).
Oye(Oye), Nagata(Nagata).
What are(在) you doing here?
Is the universe
about to end again?
Did(过) you think
I'd miss a chance
to talk to you in real time?
Good to see you, kopeng.
A bit of a surprise
to be seen(看到).
The Inners(的) don't shoot us
to pieces(片) with their railguns.
We don't nuke(核武器攻击) the Ring.
One big happy family now,
I guess.
You've been(一直) busy, eh?
Over 40(40) Ring comm relays(继电器)
installed(的) to date, I gather.
Forty-two,
which means only 1,331
to go.
With Medina(麦地那) Station
the hub(中心) of it all.
It's a good command.
Only gas station
on the new frontier.
We're putting(推杆) in
a souvenir(纪念品) shop
Be a lot of business
after the blockade(封锁) lifts(电梯).
- How is your back?
- Only hurts( ) when I move.
Which means nerves(神经) are(是)
regrowing(再生), so that's good.
You're bound for Ilus.
That's right.
With James Holden
on the gunship(武装直升机).
You're going to get
the Belters(Belters) off that planet.
We're not going
to evict(驱逐) anyone
We're going to make sure
it's safe
Safe?
You hear how many
of those refugees(难民)
died(死) trying(尝试) to adapt?
A lot of them had(的) to go
back up to orbit.
They were(曾经) foolish to think
they could live there.
It's not foolish
to want free air
and free water
and a home for their children(孩子).
We are(是) creatures(生物) of space.
In two generations(代),
their children(孩子) will be Inners(的).
They won't even remember
what they were(曾经)wont(习惯)y won't even remember
what they were.
Everyone should have the right
to decide for themselves.
Of course.
Xalte to sif(特), Camina.
Dewe( ) fasi( ), Nagata(Nagata).
We won't be able to assess
how badly the Belterwont(的)won't be able to assess
how badly the Belters(的)
have contaminated(污染)
the atmosphere
until we've actually
been(一直) on the planet,
but once you're there,
I'm hoping(希望) we can
convince them of the need
to limit the damage.
I'm looking(看) forward to working
with you, Captain.
We'll see you on New Terra(地).
We're through the RingWere(过)re through the Ring.
Be on Ilus in a few weeks.
Then what?
I'll let you know.
Thanks for the ride.
What...what are(是) we supposed...
Wait!
Got something you want
to say to me, sailor(水手)?
Can I...
Can I buy you another beer?
Got RIF'd about
six months(月) back.
They told our whole unit,
"Hey, thanks for the memories(回忆).
You're all civilians(平民) now."
Had(曾经) a promotion coming up too.
That's the shit end
of the stick.
You should know.
I watched(过) your hearing
on the feed.
You could've saved(的)
your benefits(福利) if you signed(签字的)
that statement they were(的)
waving(的) in front of you.
I'm sure it was
good entertainment.
- But you wouldn't.
- I stand by what I did(的),
and I can live
with the fallout(果).
That's what a Marine does(的).
First they order you to lie.
Then they strip you
of your pension,
your skin,
when you put honor(荣誉) first.
And he doesn't bitch(婊子) and whine(发)
when the chips(薯条) are(在) down.
He goes(人) to the VA,
gets(得到) a regular job...
I'm there every goddamn(该死的) day
waiting(等候) in line.
The problem is, you've got
too much time to think.
- It's making(制造) you crazy.
- Crazy?
- Yeah.
- Me crazy?
- Mm-hmm.
You look like you're
about ready to vent(发泄)
someone's skull for
looking(有) at you the wrong waysomeones(有人)'s skull for
looking at you the wrong way.
You're not exactly the
poster girl for mental health.
I didn't vent( ) yours.
Oh, bleeding(流血) heart.
Let me ask you something.
You were(曾经) inside
that Ring station.
What did(曾经) you see?
Nothing that would make sense,
except a bunch of people
killing each other
to control something
they didn't even understand.
Tell you what, sailor(水手).
Hang on to that uniform.
Keep in tip-toptiptop(最)on to that uniform.
Keep in tip-top.
You can be damn sure there are(是)
plenty more wars(战争) coming.
Beltalowda
would be wise to ask,
if now we kill our own
on order of the Inners(内),
is this peace
worth the price?
The OPA does(有) not
speak for all.
And those who stand
with Fred Johnson
and Anderson Dawes
should bear in mind
the inevitable fate of
wellwalla and collaborators(的).
Tynan, you're entering(进入)
the Ring Blockade(封锁) Zone.
Please transmit
your access code.
Tynan, no entry
to the Ring is permitted(允许)
without proper authorization(授权).
Transmit your access code
immediately.
Bossmang, they target-lock us.
Tynan, this is
your final warning.
Ah, give it to them.
Code verified(证).
Tynan, you're cleared(清除)
for the Ring.
Ashford.
What?
We have enough
problems(的) already
without you
agitating(不) the Inners(内部).
Well, they like humiliating(羞) us.
It's bad enough I have to play
cop(警) to protect their haulers(搬运工).
- We have a treaty.
- Worth what to the Belt?
We'll find out, keya(凯亚)?
You have to trust your gut(的).
Well, the last time
I did(的) that,
it did(曾经)n't work out so well,
did it?
We were(曾经) all flying blind,
Pampaw.
Yeah, well,
me more than you.
Only because my friend
had(有) a boyfriend
with an imaginary(想) friend
who told us how to power
that station down.
And I thought
he was a madman(疯子).
But he...he turns(转弯) out
to be a prophet(先知).
It's possible to be both.
Why'd I let you
talk me into this?
Are(是吗) you kidding(玩笑)?
First scientists(科学家) ever
to study a whole new biome(生物群落).
We're making(在) historyWere(曾经是)re making history.
Maybe you will.
This planet has(有)
no geological(地质) activity.
And isn't that amazingisnt(不是) isn't that amazing?
I was with the Hygeia(亚) group
when we found some Belters(的)
squatting(蹲) on a rock
with a billion in platinum(铂) ore(矿)
- that we had(的) the charter for.
- How'd that go?
We gave(的) them a percentage
of the take, 300K,
topped(的) off their water tanks(的),
sent(的) them on their way.
You got off cheap.
Yeah, the company
called(的) it a win.
Well, let's hope
it's that easy herelets(让)l, let's hope
it's that easy here.
Yeah, we've got a legal charter
from the UN and Mars, so...
You think the OPA(管理局)
give a shit about that?
No, I do not.
Lighten(松) up, Fayez.
You're about to be famous.
Bet the rocks(石) down here look
just like the ones(一个) back home.
Well, I'll name a new bug
after you.
Hold tight!
There's one over hereTheres(有)'s one over here!
Give me the mask!
All right.
Twenty-three
of our people are(人) dead,
including
the mission commander
and the ship's physicianships(船)the ship's physician.
The heavy lift shuttle
was destroyed(被),
along with most
of the expedition's supplies(物).
Security Chief Murtry
refused(拒绝) evacuation(撤)
and is now in operational
command of the expedition.
Cause of the crash
is currently unknown.
The Belters(Belters) are(在)
providing(提供) what aid they can
but hasten(赶) to add
the company had(有) no right
to land in the first place.
It could have been(一直)
an accident or attack
or something much worse(的事).
The story is already
metastasizing(转移) on newsfeeds.
Just get yourself to Ilus,
do your job,
and let RCE( ) do theirs(他们的).
The Belters(的) will try
to enlist(取) you to their cause.
Holden, do not put
your dick in it.
It's fucked enough already.
It's good advice.
Cap, test fire lined(衬里) up.
Fire at will.
Take that, blue goo(粘).
Belte hero.
You na kang let them take us
from our land.
This our home.
This our land, huh?
This Belter(的) land.
Nobody's doing anything
to anybody.
We're here to helpWere(的)re here to help.
Welcome.
Carol(欢) Chiwewe.
I'm the administrator
of the settlement.
- Jim Holden.
Captain Holden.
Chief Murtry.
Welcome to New Terra(地).
Come with me. I'll give you
the lay of the land.
Good to meet you.
Hey, you here fo help us
or help them?
All right, all right,
easy there, partner.
Traitors(叛徒)!
Traitor(叛徒).
Traitor.
Traitor(叛徒)!
Whoa(哇), whoa(哇)!
Whoa(哇), whoa(哇), whoa.
Everybody put
your guns(枪) down now!
- Amos, you too.
- Him(他) first.
You've got two seconds(秒).
Pashang, you got one.
What the fuck(操) is that?
Take cover!
You okay?
Amos.
Son of a bitch(狗).
Jesus.
- What the fuck(操) was that?
Hey, you okay?